## **Kobiljon Toshnazarov**

1201, 100 High-Tech building Inha-ro, Nam-Gu Incheon South Korea Personal Webpage +8210 5034 2705 kobiljon@nsl.inha.ac.kr

#### **OBJECTIVE:**

A challenging software engineering position that deeply utilizes algorithms and critical thinking (i.e., Android/iOS Software Engineering, Web Back-End Engineering, Microservices Engineering, etc.)

### SUMMARY:

Gained exposure to key concepts of Computer Science and Engineering as a graduate researcher in the Networked Systems Lab<sup>1</sup>. Also, prior to graduate school, gained professional experience in industry by working as a Software Engineer in IUTLab<sup>2</sup>, and conducting a club of programmer students in Inha University in Tashkent.

### SKILLS / KEYWORDS:

- C++ (from 98 till 17), Kotlin, Java (7, 8), Python, C#, SQL, Swift, TypeScript
- REST, SOAP, Git, CircleCl, gRPC, Django, Xamarin, Ionic, Spring, Hibernate, Windows Presentation Foundation (WPF), Docker, Adobe Photoshop, Latex, OS proficiency (Mac OS/Linux/Windows)
- Algorithms (problem solving), Android application development, Microservice
- Confidence, Time management, Focus, Friendliness and manners, Work ethics, Public speaking, Research

### **EDUCATION:**

- Bachelor's Degree, 2018, Computer Science and Engineering (GPA 3.42 / 4.5), INHA UNIVERSITY in Tashkent (IUT), Uzbekistan
- Master's Degree, 2020, Computer Science and Engineering (GPA 3.86 / 4.5), INHA UNIVERSITY, Incheon, South Korea

#### MASTER'S RESEARCH THESIS TITLE

"IMSP: an Intelligent Mobile Sensing Platform for Automatized Abnormal Behavior Detection"

#### **EXPERIENCE:**

Graduate Research Assistant, Networking Systems Lab in INHA University, South Korea, full-time 2018-Present Involved in research projects:

- EasyTrack (conference MobiSys 2019) a large scale sensor data collection platform for researchers
- <u>MindForecaster</u> (conference CHI 2020) mobile application to help users prepare for stressful events using personalized interventions
- IMSP (conference KICS 2020)
- EDD, SNMP/GOOSE KERI<sup>3</sup> network failure monitoring platform, in collaboration with KERI (outsourced project)
- <u>오늘하루</u> A cognitive behavioral therapy program to improve various psychological difficulties (outsourced project)
- etc.

## Lecture Assistant in INHA University, South Korea, part-time 2018-2019

- Conducted laboratory courses for Application Programming in Java (201802CSE2107001, and 201901CSE2107001)
- Conducted laboratory courses for ComputerNetworks (201902CSE4202001)

## Software Engineer, IUTLab Tashkent, Uzbekistan, part-time 2016-2017

- Developed Windows and Android client applications (i.e., Kadrlar, MindWind, etc.)
- Used: C#, Java, Maven, PostgreSQL, Git, Firebase, Android Studio, Eclipse, Microsoft Visual Studio

### PC & Mobile Phone Repair Assistant Technician, Kashkadarya Uzbekistan, part-time 2009-2011

- Repaired mobile phones (hardware and software)
- Did OS installations (Windows XP)
- Assembled / disassembled PCs and mobile phones

More details about my work are available on this page.

### LANGUAGE SKILLS

English - fluent (active IELTS 7.5 / 9) Russian & Uzbek - bilingual (native)

Korean - intermediate (able to conduct non-complex conversations)

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>1</sup> nsl.inha.ac.kr (INHA University, South Korea)

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>2</sup> iutlab.uz (Tashkent, Uzbekistan)

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>3</sup> Korean Electricity Research Institute

### **PUBLICATIONS**

- EasyTrack Orchestrating Large-scale Mobile User Experimental Studies (2019), MobiSys'19 Proceedings
- IMSP an Intelligent Mobile Sensing Platform for Automatized Abnormal Behavior Detection (2020), KICS Winter Conference 2020 (under publication)
- Toward Future-Centric Personal Informatics: Expecting Stressful Events and Preparing Personalized Interventions in Stress Management (2019), CHI'20 Proceedings (under publication)

### LABORATORY PROJECTS DETAILS (MS, INHA University)

- EasyTrack Orchestrating Large-scale Mobile User Experimental Studies (2019), MobiSys'19 Proceedings
  - Duty created a generic purpose, large-scale sensor data collection platform for Mobile and Wearable devices; and conducted a preliminary observation on detection of abnormal behavior of participants using Density Based LOF technique.
  - o Tools Latex, Django, gRPC, LOF, MongoDB, Google Play Services, Tizen SDK, Gnuplot, Maven, Git
- Toward Future-Centric Personal Informatics: Expecting Stressful Events and Preparing Personalized Interventions in Stress Management (2019), CHI'20 Proceedings (under publication)
  - Duty created a Web API server and Android client application for sensor data collection; and conducted a mobile user study on effectiveness of interventions on reduction of stress levels.
  - o Tools Latex, oAuth 2.0, PostgreSQL, Google Play Services, Gnuplot, Django, Git
- EDD Early Depression Detection with Passive Sensing (source-code)
  - Duty created a Web server using Django framework that collects passive sensing data from participant devices:
  - o Tools Latex, Weka, Django, PostgreSQL, Gnuplot, Git
- 오늘하루<sup>4</sup> Cognitive behavioral therapy program to improve various psychological difficulties
  - o Duty developed a cross-platform (iOS/Android) application using Ionic SDK (on top of AngularJS, and Apache Cordova) by the request of Yonsei University (<a href="mailto:vonseiharu@gmail.com">vonseiharu@gmail.com</a>).
  - o Tools Ionic, MySQL, Git
- SNMP KERI Network node failure monitoring platform, in collaboration with 한국전기연구원 (<u>source-code</u>)
  - Duty created a platform (for Windows OS) that utilizes SNMP protocol to acquire each station's network usage statistics; and tested in a laboratory environment in 한국전기연구원.
  - o Tools WinForms, SnmpSharpNet, WireShark, Git
- GOOSE KERI Network link failure monitoring platform, in collaboration with 한국전기연구원. (<u>source-code</u>)
  - Duty Created a platform (for Windows OS) that captures GOOSE packets within a PRP/HSR networks, utilizing the hardware address stamped in the GOOSE packets to detect broken links within the networks; and tested the platform in a laboratory environment in 한국전기연구원.
  - o Tools WinForms, SharpPcap, WireShark, Git
- DARCA Dynamic Association Regulator Considering Airtime over SDN-enabled WiFi (<u>source-code</u>)
  - o Created a virtual wireless network topology on ns-3; and modified existing TCP to perform a hard-handover of a station between APs triggered by decreasing RSSI values when a station nearby one AP moves away, and approaches another AP within a wireless network.
  - o Tools Latex, ns-3, WireShark, Gnuplot, Git

### SCHOOL PROJECTS (BS, INHA University in Tashkent)

- LabEx a labyrinth-explorer toy car equipped with ATMega128A microcontroller that solves physical labyrinths using the "right-hand rule" maze solving algorithm<sup>5</sup>.
- MyWeek personalized calendar-based application that uses a Backpropagation NN<sup>6</sup> to learn user's preferences (choices of time) on calendar events by categorizing them (i.e., football match, watching movies, meet friends, etc.), and suggests possible time slots during event creation.
- Fimetable a flexible timetable generator application for academic institutions that automatically generates and suggests possible timetables that match institution's criteria (i.e., availability, capacity, etc.).

# **CONFERENCES**

- KICS Winter Conference (Feb. 5th Feb. 7th, 2020), Yongpyong Resort, Pyeongchang, South Korea
- MobiSys2019: The 17<sup>th</sup> ACM International Conference on Mobile Systems, Applications and Services (June 17th June 21st, 2019), Coex Gangnam, Seoul, South Korea
- HCI KOREA 2019: 충간笑음 Surfing on the New Wave (Feb. 13th Feb 16th, 2019), Jeju Island ICC (International Convention Center). South Korea
- SparkLabs Demo Day (June 30th, 2017), Coex, Seoul, South Korea
- SIGCHI Korea Local Chapter 2018, Spring Academic Workshop (April 13th, 2018), KAIST Daejeon, South Korea

٠

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>4</sup> Source-code could not be shared due to privacy concerns by Yonsei University; website: haruasd.net

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>5</sup> Right-hand rule: en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maze\_solving\_algorithm

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>6</sup> NN: Neural Network